Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Records WAG 006
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Other boxes which will eventually form part of this series (notably the files of David Linvingston) have been described in Series IX, below.
SERIES IX: UNPROCESSED MATERIAL, 1930s-1995.
One hundred six boxes of unprocessed material, described to the box level only, cover the period from the late 1930s to 1991, and include general and office files, shop files, records of UAW, Local 2110, Legal Department records, materials dealing with the UAW merger (1982-1987), and files of long-time president David Livingstone and staff members Frank Brown and Roger Keeran.
NOTE: This collection is housed offsite and advance notice is required for use, with the exception of the first two series, which are available on microfilm (R-7450).
Arrangement
Folders are generally arranged alphabetically; minutes are arranged chronologically
The records are arranged in nine series:
Missing Title
I. Minutes, 1933-1970
II. Counsel Files, 1944-1974
III. Finance Department, 1940-1964
IV. Affiliates, 1937-1950
V. Grievances and Arbitration Dispositions, 1940-1969
VI. Subject Files, 1938-1979
VII. Shop Files, 1937-1971
VIII. Officers' Files, 1933-1992
IX. Unprocessed Material, 1930s-1995.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Archives
United AutomobileWorkers of America, District 65 Oral Histories (OH 019)
Separated Material
Photographs were separated to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs (PHOTOS 023).
Correspondence, miscellaneous documents, ephemera and clippings from Cleveland Robinson, Secretary-Treasurer of the United Auto Workers of America District 65 from 1952-1992, were separated to the Cleveland Robinson Papers (WAG 006.001).
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York.; Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Clippings (information artifacts); Clothing trade |z New York (State) |z New York.; Labor laws and legislation -- United States.; Reports.; Speeches.; Labor unions |x Clerks (Retail trade) |z New York (State) |z New York.; Labor unions -- Printing industry -- New York (State) -- New York.; Minorities |x Employment |z New York (State) |z New York.; Jews |x Employment.; Warehouses -- New York (State) -- New York.; Dry-goods |z New York (State) |z New York.; Labor unions |x Shoemakers |z New York (State) |z New York.; Briefs (legal documents); Labor unions |x Paper box industry |z New York (State) |z New York.; Minorities |x Employment |z United States.; Contracts; Collective bargaining -- United States.; Lists (document genres); Labor unions |x White collar workers |z New York (State) |z New York.; Labor -- United States.; Notes.; Minutes (administrative records); Women |x Employment |z United States.; Advertisements.; Inventories.; Osman, Arthur.; Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union; Robinson, Cleveland L. (Cleveland Lowellyn), 1914-1995; United Automobile, Aircraft, and Vehicle Workers of America. District 65; Livingston, David; National Association of Women's and Children's Apparel Salesmen; Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.); United Office and Professional Workers Association; Rogow, Robert.; Citizen's Commission on the Economy; United States. Labor Management Relations Act, 1947; Drug Trade Salesmen's Union; Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers Union; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. District 65
- Series I: Minutes, 1933-1969
  - Executive Board Minutes, Nov 1933-Dec 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Executive Board (and General Stewards) Minutes, Jan 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - General Membership Minutes, Sep 1933-Dec 1934, May 1936-Sep 1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Membership Minutes, Oct 1937-Nov 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - General Council Minutes, Jan 1943-Dec 1947 (Box 1, Folder 10-19)
  - General Council Minutes, Feb 1948-Jun 1954 (Box 2, Folder 1-17)
  - General Council Minutes, Jul 1954-Dec 1962 (Box 3, Folder 1-17)
  - General Council Minutes, Jan 1963-Dec 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1-13)
  - Executive Council Minutes, 1955-1960 (Box 4, Folder 14-21)
  - Executive Council Minutes, 1961-1968 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - General Council Proceedings, 1941-1948 (Box 5, Folder 3-16)
  - General Council Proceedings, Sep 1969-Oct 1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Stewards' Council Proceedings, Apr 1943-Jun 1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Committee Reports, 1938-1941 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - General Stewards' Meetings--Incomplete, 1939-1941, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committee Reports, 1940-1942 (Box 6, Folder 4-7)
  - Harlem Dance Committee, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Invasion Drive, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
  - Downtown Division; Downtown Staff Meetings, Division Membership Meetings, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Downtown Division D-1 Stewards Meeting D-1 Section Membership Meeting, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Downtown Division D-2 Section Stewards Meetings D-2 Membership Meeting, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Downtown Division D-3 Section Stewards Meetings D-3 Membership Meeting, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Downtown Division, Section Stewards Meeting D-4 D-5 D-6 Section Membership Meeting, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Organizing Committee, 1940-1942 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
  - Eastside -- I-V, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
  - Downtown & Downtown I-VI, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Uptown & Uptown I-IV, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Midtown & Midtown I-IV, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn & Brooklyn I-III, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Long Island, Long Island I-II & Bronx, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Various Committees of Stewards & Exec Board, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 25-26)
  - Division Directors Meetings, 1943-1944 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Uptown Division Minutes, 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 2-4)
  - Eastside Division Minutes, 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 5-8)
  - Midtown Division Minutes, 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 9-11)
  - Brooklyn, L.I. and N.J. Minutes, 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 12-14)
  - Wholesale Division Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 15-18)
  - Wholesale Division Minutes, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Warehouse Division General Minutes, Sep 1945-May 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Warehouse Division Minutes, Jun 1947-May 1905 (Box 8, Folder 5-14)
  - Dry Goods Division Minutes, 1943-1947 (Box 8, Folder 15-17)
  - Dry Goods Division (Midtown) Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Processing Division Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 2-6)
  - General Processing Division Minutes Membership Meetings, Aug 1943-Apr 1947 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - General Processing Division Minutes Executive Board, Aug 1943-May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
  - Garment Supply Division Minutes Membership Meetings, Aug 1943-May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
  - Garment Supply Division Minutes Executive Board Meetings, Jul 1943-May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Garment Supplies Division Executive Board and Membership Meeting, Feb 1946-May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Garment Supplies Division (B Subdivision), 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - Apparel Division, 1943-1946 (Box 9, Folder 17-19)
  - Food & Drug Division, 1943-1947 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
  - Paper Products Division, 1943-1947 (Box 10, Folder 4-7)
  - Needle Processing Division, 1944-1947 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - Footwear Division, 1943-Apr (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
  - Drug Trade Salesmen Union, 1943-1948 (Box 10, Folder 12-16)
  - Hardware China & Novelties, 1944-1947 (Box 10, Folder 17-20)
  - Area Minutes, 5th Ave., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Area Minutes, 4th Ave., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Area Minutes, Upper B'way, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Area Minutes, Garment, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Area Minutes, West Side, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Area Minutes, City Hall, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Area Minutes, Headquarters, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Area Minutes, Midtown, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Area Minutes, Brooklyn, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Area Minutes, Long Island, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Area Minutes, New Jersey, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Area Minutes, Bronx & Upper Manhattan, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Area Minutes, 5th Ave, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Area Minutes, 4th Ave, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Area Minutes, Broadway, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Area Minutes, West Side, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Area Minutes, City Hall, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Area Minutes, Headquarters, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Area Minutes, Midtown, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Area Minutes, Brooklyn, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Area Minutes, Long Island, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Area Minutes, New Jersey, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Area Minutes, Bronx, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Area Minutes, Garment, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Area Minutes Chelsea-Greenwich Port Authority, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Area Minutes, City Hall Wall Street, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Area Minutes, Duffy Sq Theatre, Upper Man. Upper W-S, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Area Minutes, East Bronx, S. Bronx, W. Bronx, Westchester, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Area Minutes, Jersey City, Patterson, Bell, Bergen, Newark, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Area Minutes, Boro Hall, Bush Term. Coney Island, Williamsburg, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Area Minutes, Bryant Park, Herald Sq Lower Gmt, Radio City, Times Sq, Upper Gmt, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Area Minutes Canal St Headquarters, Lower E.S. Spring St, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Area Minutes 14th St, Gramercy, 23d St Union Sq., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Area Minutes 4th Ave, Grand C Madison Sq, Upper E.S., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Area Minutes, Greenpoint, Jamaica, Nassau, Suffolk, Queens Plaza, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Area Minutes, East Bronx, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Area Minutes, West Bronx, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Area Minutes, Westchester, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Area Minutes, Jersey City, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Area Minutes, Newark, Patterson, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Area Minutes, Boro Hall, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Area Minutes, Bush Term, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Area Minutes, Coney Island, East New York, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Area Minutes, Williamsburg, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Area Minutes, Bryant Park, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Area Minutes, Herald Square, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Area Minutes, Lower Gmt., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Area Minutes, Radio City, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Area Minutes, Times Square, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Area Minutes, Upper Gmt., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Area Minutes, East Bronx, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Area Minutes, Chelsea, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Area Minutes, Greenwich, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Area Minutes, Port Authority, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Area Minutes, City Hall, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Area Minutes, Wall Street, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Area Minutes, Upper Manhattan, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Area Minutes, Upper Westside, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Area Minutes, 4th Ave, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Area Minutes, Grand Central, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Area Minutes, Madison Sq., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Area Minutes, Upper Eastside, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Area Minutes, Jamaica, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Area Minutes, Greenpoint, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Area Minutes, Nassau, Suffolk, Queens Pl, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Area Minutes, Canal Street, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Area Minutes, Headquarters, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Area Minutes, Lower Manhattan, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Area Minutes, Spring St, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Area Minutes, 14th St, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Area Minutes, Midtown, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Area Minutes, Stuyvestant, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Area Minutes, Union Square, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Area Minutes, 4th Ave., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Area Minutes, Madison Square, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Area Minutes, Upper East Side, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Area Minutes, Greenpoint, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Area Minutes, Jamaica Nassau, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Area Minutes, Queens Plaza, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Area Minutes, Boro Hall, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Area Minutes, Bush Terminal, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Area Minutes, Westside, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Area Minutes, Upper Manhattan, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Area Minutes, Upper Bronx, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Area Minues, Newark, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Area Minutes, Jersey City, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Area Minutes, Brooklyn/Jersey I-V, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 20-24)
  - Area Minutes, Canal Street, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Area Minutes, Headquarters, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Area Minutes, Lower Manhattan, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Area Minutes, Spring Street, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Area Minutes, Downtown I-V, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 29-33)
  - Area Minutes, Herald Square, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Area Minutes, Garment, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Area Minutes, Times Square, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Area Minutes, Uptown, I-VII, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 37-43)
  - Area Minutes, Stuyvestant, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Area Minutes, Midtown I-II, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 45-46)
  - Area Minutes, Midtown III-V, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
  - Area Minutes, Bronx/Long Island Div I-V, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - Area Minutes, Downtown I-V, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 6-10)
  - Area Minutes, Uptown I-VII, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 11-17)
  - Area Minutes, Midtown I-IV, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 18-21)
  - Area Minutes, Bronx/Long Island I-IV, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 22-25)
  - Area Minutes Local 144, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Area Minutes, Brooklyn/New Jersey I-V, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 27-31)
  - Local 121, 1949-1951 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Department Store, Local 2, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 3, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 5, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 11, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 1250, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 1250B/ Warehouse Membership Mtg., 1950 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 2, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 3, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 5, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 11, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 1250, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 1250B, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Warehouse Local, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 2, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 3, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 5 & 11, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 1250, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 1250B, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Warehouse, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 2, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 3, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 5, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 1250, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Local Minutes, Department Store Local 1250B, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Cotton, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Textile, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Garment Supplies, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Buttons, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Milliney Knitwear, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Upholstery, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Jewelry, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Quilt & Interlining, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Toys & Gifts, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Outside Salesmen, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Chain, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Apparel, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Sample Card, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Cosmetic/Drug, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Miscellaneous Warehouse, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Miscellaneous Paper, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, 2d Hand Clothing, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, NY Corrugated, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Metal, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, China, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Suspender, Garter Misc., 1949 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Retail/Lumber, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Department Store Council Minutes, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Cotton, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Textile, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Garment Supplies, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Button, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Millinery Knitwear, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Industry Executive Board Meeting, Knitwear, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Toy Gift Hardware & Jewelry, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Outside Salesmen, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Apparel, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Cosmetics, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Food & Misc Warehouse, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Corrugated, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Processing, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Paint & Lumber, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Retail, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Local 121, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Local 144, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, News, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Drug Trade, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Radio, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Insurance, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Screen, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Finance, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, General Office, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Cashier, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Textile, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Garment Supplies, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Button, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Millinery, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Knitwear, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Chain & Home Office, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Cosmetic Drug, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Misc. & General Warehouse, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Corrugated, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Processing, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Paint & Lumber, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Retail, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Local 144, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, NYSS, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Screen/News, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Direct Mail, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, General Office, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Finance, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Book, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Dental, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods Salesmen, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Garment Supplies, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Shoe, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Textile, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Hardware, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Chain & Home Office, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Cosmetic, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Miscellaneous Warehouse, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Corrugated, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Processing, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Lumber, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Retail, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Local 144, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Cigar, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Direct Mail I-II, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 62-63)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Food, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Dry Goods, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Metal Misc, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Industry Executive Board Minutes, Needle Processing, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Industry Minutes, Screen, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 68)